I want to do it.
I want to have s...
"S"?
Soap. I'll go wash my hands with soap.
I can't ask about sex the moment he wakes up.
Nope. Definitely not.
But...
Maybe if I pop the question
at the right timing?
Ouji.
Do you... want to drink some wine?
Sure, let's crack open a bottle.
Alright.
I was super nervous.
I was just saying whatever at some point.
Thankfully, Saiki helped fill in the gaps.
I'm being hired as this girl's producer.
Really? I see her in a ton of magazines.
Do you think she's cute?
Not really.
"Then who do you think is cute?"
"Me?"
Perfect. The natural follow-up question.
Or is it?
No, you're deluding yourself.
Huh?
Nothing.
Weirdo.
If anything...
Do you even have a sex drive now?
[Episode 3]
Huh?
A sex drive?
Me?
- I misspoke.
- Really? I'm not entirely convinced.
Sorry, my brain's a mess right now, and...
Honestly, not for these last few years, no.
- What?
- Maybe it's my age.
I was a little too active in my youth.
You... You think?
Well, that's not the only reason.
It's just easy being with you, Haru.
I'm going to bed.
Night.
Being with you is so easy.
That doesn't make me happy at all.
I'll go fill the bath for us.
Okay.
[6 Months Earlier]
I'll be applying your toner.
Yamaguchi, we can't style 20 actors
in an hour!
I promise it's possible.
Some kids do their own finishing touches.
Fuyumi, how's my eyeliner? Looking good?
They're not even in the slightest.
Show me how I can improve.
I won't expect results,
or anything in return.
I'm simply letting my heart and body
savor this moment.
Affirming myself in this manner,
is so alleviating.
What a poet.
[Haru: I failed...]
Was that notification from your husband?
Nope. A friend.
She had this long,
one-sided crush on a musician,
only for him to suddenly propose to her.
They got married the other day.
Sounds like a story out of a fairy tale.
But it might not be going well for them.
Why not?
Isn't this their "happily ever after"?
Life doesn't "end" so simply like in stories.
Romance, marriage,
both can become shackles
if you're fixated on them.
What the...
You were thinking of your husband.
That makes me jealous.
Will you stay the night today?
I can't.
I'll go home.
You have a photoshoot tomorrow.
You need to sleep early, and prep.
You're not my stylist tomorrow though.
I have other jobs to do.
I'm not your exclusive makeup artist, Shota.
I'll become famous enough to request for you.
Don't mix business
with personal matters, okay?
I wasn't trying to mix them together.
Sure, I may have a slightly ulterior motive.
But when you did my makeup for a shoot,
it was a smash hit.
- Really?
- Yeah.
People said I looked sexy.
That's good to hear.
I owe it to your magic touch.
You don't need to stay the night.
But can you stay a bit longer?
Nope.
[Keiko Kotani]
[Having fun "playing marriage"?]
I'm home.
Welcome back!
- Huh?
- Home already?
Yeah. I wrapped up earlier today.
Chizuka, what happened to your sleepover?
The Sato's called to cancel.
Apparently, Yui caught a fever.
I see.
Did you two eat already?
Yeah. We had dinner at a diner.
I see.
Something the matter?
Nothing.
Just pondering the big job I finished.
Here's to hoping your next job
is catered more to your skills.
You used to style for big advertisements
and major magazines, right?
Right.
Maybe I'll lobby for a better opportunity.
[New message from Haru]
Do you even have a sex drive now?
Not for these last few years, no.
What?
For you.
Thanks.
Sleep-deprived?
Maybe I should've bought coffee.
No, you wouldn't drink that.
Yeah.
I don't do well with bitter things.
I'm surprised you knew.
We've worked together for a while now.
That, we have.
Something on your mind?
I'm here to listen.
"My newlywed husband has no sex drive."
Like I could just blurt that out.
It's nothing. Thanks though.
I can meet for lunch, if you want.
[Fuyumi]
You asked him if he had a sex drive?
If he's got none, then what do I even do?
Gosh... to think your Ouji has no drive...
I don't feel any better, by the way.
You said accepting my feelings would help.
If anything, I feel more confused.
I guess I should say, "I'm sorry"?
Even if I want to do it, we can't.
He has no sex drive! None!
Inside voices, Haru!
It's still the middle of the day!
I even bought a king-sized bed for my room...
B-But... I think you've actually
made some progress.
Until now,
you were thinking about this yourself.
But now you've opened up to him!
Though it might have raised
a few more questions...
I didn't want to raise more questions.
Now to figure out how to reignite his drive.
You make it sound so simple.
It's a high hurdle to overcome.
Walls in front of you may look tall.
But at least there's a wall you can see!
Such positivity.
You'll just have to overcome it.
- A tall wall...
- You'll just have to overcome it.
Haru?
I...
I have a sex drive.
- Huh?
- Don't "huh?" me!
We're married. I love you.
Take me!
I want to have sex with you!
Will putting it in satisfy you?
That felt too real.
More pressingly, I can't believe I...
My bad.
Ouji, in a suit? What a feast for the eyes!
Wait, I'm not wearing anything underneath.
Lock the door, would you?
Only old dramas do the whole,
"bathroom surprise" plot.
Sorry.
The suit looks nice on you.
Thanks. I'm seeing some higher-ups
at that idol's recording session.
I'll probably be home late tonight.
Yes, I totally understand.
If you're comfortable enough
to laugh off the awkwardness,
finding happiness without sex
is entirely possible, isn't it?
Is it?
What are your honest feelings, Haru?
I...
I want to do it.
Do what?
Nothing, pay me no mind.
If you insist.
They cannot ever have sex again,
unless they divorce their husbands.
Isn't that incredibly terrifying for a woman?
Welcome.
Haru?
Akina?
You're drinking alone? That's unusual.
I needed the alcohol.
What? You haven't had sex with Ouji?
I know you think it's ridiculous,
given we're newlyweds.
I haven't said anything yet.
I know, but what can I do?
He's saying he has no sex drive.
It's probably just withered dry.
- What?
- Water it, and he'll perk right back up.
You're giving high level advice, too?
Is it really high level though?
Unlike romance, sex is simple.
He lusts, you're lusted after,
and you both satiate those desires.
That's why I love it.
It's the "lusted after" part I struggle with.
He didn't even react
when I wore nothing but a sweater.
Then I guess you'll just have to try harder.
I can't.
To have lust, and to be lusted for.
They're supposed to be equal, right?
That, they are.
But we've never been equal.
Ouji was always at the center of everything.
I could only ever watch from the sidelines.
Sometimes, I wasn't even permitted a glance.
Ouji...
You're a bit too persistent.
Ouji was the main character.
And I was the background extra.
Ouji controls the flow of the story.
You don't give yourself any credit.
Haru, do you want to have sex?
Or do you want to be loved by your husband?
If it's the latter,
then I can't say I really get it.
Unlike sex, romance is never simple,
even if you are a married couple.
Personally, I hate conflating
my bodily desires with that of the heart.
I'm surprised you can keep them apart.
Sure, you may want to have sex,
but only with your husband, right?
Of course. I never considered another option.
And you also want to share
a mutual love with him, right?
Right.
Then you're not helping your case,
calling yourself a background extra.
Why'd you even marry him in the first place?
I married Ouji because he proposed to me.
Sounds like he loves you plenty.
That's not the issue here.
Not for these last few years, no.
- What?
- Well, that's not the only reason.
It's just easy being with you, Haru.
He says being with me, is "easy".
Easy.
Maybe he's tired
dealing with aggressive women?
You are the more demure type.
Akina. You can learn to be less blunt.
Sorry.
Maybe he never saw me
with that intent at all.
Say something.
You told me to be less blunt.
That never stopped you before.
Still, this is only your current predicament.
You never know what the future holds.
It's been five years since I met him.
Will he change? We haven't even held hands.
The furthest he gets is a head pat.
- I gotta go.
- That's it?
Good luck. I'm rooting for you.
- Are you, really?
- Toodles!
This is only your current predicament.
You never know what the future holds.
But after five years of nothing?
Good evening. The name's Naoki,
from Ebisu Boys Club.
Welcome home, Haruchan!
"Haruchan"? Why the nickname?
I thought you said you'd be late.
I got worn out.
Home is where I can relax.
I see.
Join me for a drink, Haruchan.
Ouji, did you make a blunder?
Huh?
You only use "chan"
when things have gone wrong.
Seriously?
Well...
Recently, a capable girl in her twenties
joined our agency.
And today, she got mad at me
for always addressing her as "you".
Just made me realize
how I sometimes do that to you, too.
You're having this realization, now?
She's entirely right, you know.
Our generation has to adapt to new standards.
I know that now, but still...
You're seriously a calming presence.
And you're doing it again!
[Preview]